Please contact turkision@gmail.com
for any inquiries
NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING
THE FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION.
Hang on, Dervish.
He is bleeding so badly.
Can we really save him?
As long as we try, Allah will heal him.
Come on. Hurry up.
Alişar!
Ya Allah!
Alişar Bey!
Open the gates now!
They are keep yelling outside.
Alişar!
What are we waiting for?
Let’s go out and fight!
Nobody will listen to us if we don’t
shut them up now.
We will.
We will cut...
...first their voice...
...then their head!
May every bite you took from my bowl be
illicit…
…if you don’t make a pond of blood out
there!
Alişar!
Open the gates!
You are going to pay for knocking on
my door like this, Gündüz.
We are not here to pay something.
We are here to shed blood!
You once seized my title by force.
My nephew, are you going to seize my life
now?
We pulled your strings...
...before you started a bloody rebellion
at our Tent.
We spoiled your game.
Don’t you ever talk, uncle!
What are you talking about, Gündüz?
Soldiers!
Arms down!
If Dündar Bey had really done something
like that…
…he would have been killed by me
already, Gündüz.
You should tell this to yourself…
…not me.
Every game he played...
...has brought shame upon our Tent.
As well as lies…
…and blood!
Do you think you left me any other
choice...
...to get what is rightfully mine?
Do you think I am stupid?
You are a fool, Dündar!
You are stupid enough to let your
daughter marry...
...the murderer of your own son!
The murderer of your son!
In the name of Allah.
My Sheikh, try not to tire yourself.
Please get some rest.
Working is a duty for all, my Zulfiqar.
Serving in the way of Allah is the most
sacred blessing reserved to men.
My Sheikh!
I hope everything is okay.
May Allah be with us.
Osman!
-My Osman!
-Osman!
-Run!
Osman!?
Osman!
My Osman! Who did this to you?
My Allah, don't make me feel this pain.
My Osman!
Thanks to Allah, he is still alive.
Build the fire immediately!
Come on, faster!
Who did this to you?
My Osman!
Who and why?
Come on, my Zulfiqar!
Give us some space.
Ya Allah!
My Allah, take my life and give it to him.
My Osman!
My Osman, what did they do to you?
Where did you find him?
Who did this, son?
We found him near Alacatepe.
He was unconcious when we found him,
my Sheikh.
Seems like he got hit by the arrow so
badly. We couldn't dare to touch it.
What are we going to do?
Move aside!
Osman!
I am trying to prevent a conflict here.
While you guys cast aspersions on me.
Attack!
Kill them all!
Enough!
Enough it is!
What do you think you are doing?
Brothers should not kill each other.
How dare you interrupt our fight?
Don’t you know no Hatun is allowed
to stick her nose into important matters?
Aygül Hatun!
Don't mistake me with those Hatuns who
serve you at your mansion, Alişar Bey!
I’m a Kayı.
Sometimes, I’m a hatun...
... sometimes, a man!
My daughter.
You threw your hijab…
…you want us to stop…
...and...
...im happy to do so.
However...
...Alişar Bey says the opposite.
You may get inside now.
Brother Gūndūz.
Bamsı Bey.
Have you lost your patience?
Why can’t you stand each other?
What is this hostility and bloodshed
about?
Aygül, my daughter…
…nobody ever wanted…
…what happened in the past.
However, seditions your father once
planted...
… has made nephews and uncles become
enemies...
…as well as father-in laws and brides.
My dear daughter, Aygül...
…I have two arrow wounds on my shoulder…
…and those very wounds are memories of…
…Burçin, who I think of as my daughter.
If that arrow had not hit you…
…would you kill my Bahadır…
…just like you killed my Batur?
Aygül.
Burçin.
You shall leave now.
Get inside.
In the name of Allah...
When I lay sick, he will take care of me
instead.
May he be healed now.
Selcan Hatun!
Is the fire ready?
Yes, my Sheikh.
How bad is his wound?
It is egregious.
If the arrow reached his lungs
we may have a hard time saving him.
We will do our best.
Allah will have the final say.
May he be healed.
He has massive bleeding, father.
Resist, my lion.
Resist.
With the name of Allah.
So that the hijab was thrown...
...It’s not honorable to fight while
neglecting our customs.
Since the swords are down...
I'll explain.
You came to my door with questions and
curiosity.
Because I neither corrupted Dündar Bey…
…nor had a role in the murder of Batur.
Now tell me…
…what do you exactly want?
From now on, you won’t interfere in our
domestic Tent affairs, Alişar.
As a banner lord, every Tent located on
this Border are connected to me.
What else can I do, Gündüz?
Grow crops?
Herd the cattle?
Now.
Alişar.
Other Tents at the Border may not say
something…
…but...
...a banner lord who interferes...
...the Bey of Kayı and his people…
...today...
…might try to interfere everyone tomorrow.
They all know about this!
This is unacceptable, Alişar.
You will pay a high price.
Gündüz Bey.
Bamsı Bey.
Once the order is broken
nobody will be able to fix it.
I suggest we meet at Söğüt tomorrow.
It’s your place and you can keep the area
safe wıth your horses.
Me and Dündar Bey will try to collaborate
with you.
Instead of swords, we will use our words.
It's a win-win situation for all.
If you ever dare to play such games
wıth us again...
…just for your information...
...we wont lay our swords down again.
Will he be okay, my Sheikh?
Only Allah knows, Hatun.
We should be positive so he'll be okay.
in the name of Allah,
the compassionate, the merciful
My Zulfiqar. Go and let the Kayı
Tent learn about his situation.
We are in responsible
of Osman Bey’s life now.
As you wish, my Sheikh
Salam Aleikum, my Sheikh.
- Salam Aleikum.
- Aleikum Salam.
Brother of Konur Alp,
Göktuğ Alp. My Sheikh.
Thanks to Allah, he is a muslim now.
Thanks to Allah.
My Sheikh...
...trails got us so far.
Is Osman Bey here?
Is he alright?
What do you think you are doing, silly?
You are ashaming me from
being your mother.
Don't you still understand...
...you are now the banner lord's wife!
You are in his mansion, under his men's
protection!
They all were going to die, stupid!
Just because I'm Alişar's wife now...
...should I forget my past?
Are Gündüz and Bamsı Bey stangers to us?
This blood will drown us all.
Don't you see?
If you are my mother...
...think about our benefit and
sit down!
But if it's like you said...
...and I'm banner lord's wife,
then, know your place!
From now, it is my words that counts
in here!
Aygül Hatun!
I thought a Bey's daughter
would know her manners...
...but you shame me in front of people...
...how can you put off your hijab...
...when you were surrounded by men!
What do you think you are doing with
this little brain of a woman!
If you know how to raise that hand...
...you should know how to use it, too.
I wouldn't want your reputation to be
shaken in front of your warriors, husband.
Come on.
Don't wander around!
Don't make me beat you!
You put off your hijab and lost my favor.
Watch your wording.
Don't lose my love, as well.
If Noyans pledge alliance to me...
...Geyhatu will see the might of
Balgay.
You are smiling.
Have you brought the news I desire?
-We did, mighty Balgay.
-Don't forget. From now...
...there is no brotherhood nor
companionship...
...there is only Balgay.
And a holy path...
...to take with Balgay.
We pledge you our lives and blood.
Speak.
Commander of Ankara, Kayseri and
Karaman...
...they are all ready to stand with you
against Geyhatu.
They wait for your word.
If it wasn't for me...
...you would be leashed by this Geyhatu...
...who can't stay sober...
...who sold his traditions to Buddha.
Then...
Move. Talha, Argun, Tuluy...
...ride your horses without a break...
...to Söğüt.
May they race with the wind and
stop only for water.
Tell them that...
Geyhatu will come to Söğüt.
Tell them to join me...
...to cut off his head.
That head of his which smiles like...
...sinister face of Buddha.
As you order, Commander Balgay.
Geyhatu sent a vanguard.
They are coming from the Karaayaz Forest.
Let's go there and see...
...what's the problem of this drunkard.
Dear Allah...
Give us the strength to bear this pain...
Don't give me the pain of losing a
child.
Don't give me the pain of
losing Osman.
My lion is burning...
I'll bring water.
Don't leave him alone.
Bala.
Keep your head up!
It's not the time to be sad.
It's time to seek Allah's help.
Osman both hears and feels us.
If you want him to wake up...
...take that tear away.
Keep your head up and wait.
Osman.
Do you really hear me?
Do you feel how my heart hurts?
I beg you, wake up.
You are my hope, luck, and future.
What can I do without you?
I will fall apart.
Don't break me further.
Wake up, I beg you.
My Allah...
...help him.
What is wrong, Zülfikar Dervish?
Welcome.
But I'm afraid it's not a
pleasant visit.
Gündüz Bey...
...Sheikh Edebali sent me.
About Osman Bey.
Osman?
Where is my brother, dervish?
Tell us.
Dervishes had found him in
the forest.
He was severely wounded when
they brought him.
Sheikh stepped in quickly. And he sent
word to you.
''He is under our protection.
Don't you worry.'' he said.
What are we waiting for, then?
We should go to Osman, right away!
Hold on, Bamsı Bey.
Hold on.
Inform Kongur Alp. Go
to Osman with the dervish.
Yes, my Bey.
Bamsı Bey, we will go to
Söğüt...
...to face Alişar.
Abdurrahman ghazi...
...the tent is under your responsibility.
-Yes, Gündüz Bey.
Dervish, don't leave Osman alone.
If you need anything...
...inform us.
May Allah help Osman...
...and reunite us, inshallah.
-Inshallah, Gündüz Bey.
-Amin.
The memory of Aybars...
...is still a wound in my heart.
Gündüz...
...I must see Osman.
I have to, Gündüz. I have to!
Bamsı Bey, if Osman was here...
...he would want you to be with me.
Do you think that there is no other
traitors than Şahin and Demirci Bey?
We are surrounded.
Time isn't our friend.
Dervish, dervish...
Bamsı Bey.
Now when you see that Osman
opens his eyes...
...when Bamsı Bey completes his
mission...
...he will come there. Say that, will you?
-Of course.
-Thank you.
These are our best soldiers, my Bey.
With a bow, they can shoot a flying bird..
...with a sword, they can slain a dragon.
Alişar Bey.
We got into this together...
We have done everything together...
How can you say that you will
kill me, too?
Revenge is a dish best served cold...
...Dündar Bey.
Don't catch fire.
Control your anger.
What kind of revenge is that?
What kind of alliance is that?
You speak of killing us,
in front of our enemies.
Don't hurry, Bahadır.
We skinned it...
...now we are on it's tail.
What is left is putting some salt
and waiting.
Killing Beys who came to my door
would bring trouble.
We will ambush Bamsı and Gündüz
on their way to Söğüt.
With my most elite troops.
They have no hope now.
While we are waiting for them...
...their dead bodies will come.
Aid! Sahibel Meydan!
May I call you with mountains and rocks...
May I call you with birds at dawn...
May I call you, my protector.
With Ayyub who has the most troubles...
...and Yakub with his tears on his eyes...
O' Muhammed! With love...
...may I call you, my protector.
With beautiful nightingales...
With followers who love Allah...
May I call you, my protector.
Aid! Tabibel-Kulub.
Dear Allah...
...I seek your protection...
...from disrespecting your words.
My Allah...
...you...
...take me and my lineage...
...to ones who sacrifice...
...for your words.
Help, Sahibel Meydan!
May I call you with mountains and rocks...
May I call you with birds at dawn...
May I call you, my protector.
With Ayyub who has the most troubles...
...and Yakub with his tears on his eyes...
O' Muhammed! With love...
...may I call you, my protector.
With Hamd ü şükrullah...
With beautiful nightingales...
With followers who love Allah...
May I call you, my protector.
Aid! Tabibel-Kulub.
Allah is the greatest.
I bear witness that there is no lord
except for Allah.
Oh my Lord.
May it be good.
In the name of Allah,
the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful.
Indeed, We have given you, [O Muhammad], a clear conquest
[Quran Al-Fath 48:1]
Allaah Almighty has spoken the truth
What is it, son?
What is bothering you?
I tried to stay awake but...
I fell asleep due to tiredness.
When I was sleeping...
I saw such a dream that...
Tell me, son.
In my dream...
A moon rose from your chest
and dive in my mine.
My chest shaked, expanded...
...and enlightened.
Then...
Something came out of my chest and
greatened so much that...
That almighty tree's branches...
...exceeded this universe...
...and arrived at beyond the seas.
It covered many realms...
...in vast lands.
I saw weapons there.
Weapons that are bloody.
I saw minarets.
On top of minarets, I saw crescents.
May it be good.
May it be good, my Sheik.
What is it?
Osman Bey...
Ertuğrul Ghazi's pride,
Dark Osman Bey.
Valiant Osman.
In your dream, you came to me, so
our Lord wants us together.
You said a moon rose from my chest
and dive in yours.
It is time.
From now on, I give permission.
Bala Hatun is your halal (permissible).
Because this is a divine sign.
Allah granted your generation Khanship,
and Sultanate.
Many places will be Islam city with your
and your generation's efforts.
Geyhatu's corrupts!
Kill them all!
Balgay! You traitor!
Damn you!
What is Geyhatu saying?
They are coming here.
They departed from Konya.
He ordered his dog Alişar to
hang Osman in Söğüt bazaar...
...and wipe Kayı Alps off.
We are going to preapre a great
welcoming ceremony to Geyhatu.
Thunder will shake Konya while...
Lightnings cover everywhere.
Come to your death, Geyhatu.
Come to your death.
I said it earlier, my daughter.
Everything has its time.
Your time to marry Osman Bey
has arrived.
Osman Bey is like a peak of a mountain.
Stand everything about him.
His way is difficult, his enemies are
tough.
Don't make a mistake while keeping
company.
Thank Lord.
You wanted my Bala for Osman earlier...
...but we didn't give her because it
was not the right time.
Now, the day has come.
Inform your tribe's almighty ones at once.
Your tribe's almighties shall come too.
There will be a marriage ceremony
as soon as possible.
The sign shows us that, when we establish
this blessed event here...
there will be
other things to establish, too.
However you deem appropriate, my Sheik.
- Thank Lord.
You talk about Söğüt Han, Alişar Bey.
What are you thinking?
Why do you have the talk there?
We wıll wait in front of Kayı Alps in
Söğütlü.
When they bring us Gündüz and Bamsı's
bodies...
No one will doubt that we did this.
What happened, Dündar Bey?
You seem unhappy.
No, I think about Osman, Alişar Bey.
What if Geyhatu forgives him?
What if he creates trouble again?
He is angry as hell, don't you know Osman?
Even if Genghiz Khan resurrect, no one
can take Osman from my hands.
He is dead now.
What is the situation, brother Boran?
They killed Kılıç Alp where Zöhre Hatun
was waiting, my Bey.
Not only that...
They also shot Bamsı Bey.
What are you talking about, Boran?
- Who shot Bamsı Bey?
- Burçin Hatun, my Bey.
What?
Burçin...
So, they poisoned Burçin too.
I am afraid that, if we don't stop them...
they will poison everyone.
- What did my brother do?
- He went to Alişar's mansion to take revenge.
However, they wanted to come to Söğüt.
They want an agreement.
Eh, black snake!
He surely knows we can't agree.
He is afriad to kill Beys in front of
his mansion.
That's why he used the.
I think they will attack, but we will
act faster than him.
My Bey, Dündar Bey will come too.
It's over now, brother.
Blood must shed!
Both my uncle's and Bahadır's death
are near.
Göktuğ.
Take Çetin with you.
Now, you'll be Kongar so that
you can approach to Balgay.
You will spy on them and tell
me where they settle.
The most important card will be
Balgay for Geyhatu.
Yes, Osman Bey.
Boran, listen to me carefully now.
Tell what I tell you to my brother.
Alişar will do his best to push us.
He will, Bamsı Bey.
What if we can't agree, son?
Then, the most honourable place
would be waiting for us.
We die with honor and be martyr instead
of obeying the cruel, in sha Allah.
Oh, my Gündüz, how beautiful you speak!
If there is shahada in the end,
we can't wait.
Let's go, son.
Let's see, whatever happens, happens.
Hey, Mashallah (praise be)
My Valiants!
Mashallah my lions!
Let's go my valiants!
Let's go, valiants!
We found them.
They even setup a base.
Çetin, inform Osman Bey.
Quite.
Come, Geyhatu.
Come and see what Erlik Khan does to you!
Balgay!
Kongar is coming.
Do you think he has Genghis Khan's laws?
Where are the Genghis Khan's laws?
That dog Osman lied again.
Boran tried to kill the Nökers
and run away.
I cut his throat.
Where is Osman?
He ran away with an arrow on his back.
As if he has 9 lives.
We'll meet again, eventually.
Focus on ending Bamsı with an arrow.
Then use your swords.
Don't let his age fool you.
He'll turn into a dragon
the moment he gets your smell.
Why aren't they here already?
Did something go wrong?
Ambush!
Soldiers!
Osman Bey...
I'll tell you everything
if you spare my life.
I beg you, don't.
I know a lot.
Another trouble begins before one ends.
But this is the last one.
Your age has started.
May your Beyhood be blessed.
Thank you, Alişar Bey.
Thank you.
I wish they left me another choice so
they wouldn't have lost their lives.
I wish they didn't ruin their lives by
following Osman and his empty dreams.
They wanted this.
They did everything to die.
Bamsı Bey, welcome!
Welcome!
Gündüz!
Bamsı Bey!
How can this be, Alişar Bey?
Something fish is going on.
It was impossible for them
to get out of that ambush alive.
I told you to be careful countless times.
What will we do now, Alişar Bey?
My Boran! Is my Osman okay?
I hope nothing is wrong.
He's okay, my Bey.
He knows that we're going to söğüt.
But my Bey said that there were traps
everywhere. Don't take the jungle route.
Go from the Alacatepe foothill.
My father was a famous Noyan
besides almighty Genghis Khan.
When Genghis Khan went to save
his wife Börti from Merkits...
... my father was with him.
While they were going to save
that almighty, powerful woman...
... do you know what
Genghis Khan said to my father?
Don't come if you're afraid.
If you'll come, don't be afraid.
Your path is my path. I won't turn back.
You raised me like Cuci,
son of the raped Börte Hatun.
My destiny with Cuci is the same.
We were both naive children.
But you protected me.
You were a father to me.
I named you while I was washing your
face with warm water in River Selengi.
You were a scared, cold, naked child.
You were nothing.
I created you from nothing.
What is that is bothering you, Balgay?
Osman?
What if he takes you from me
like Genghis Khan's laws?
I swore upon this.
I won't die without killing him.
I know.
Since you know it,
then what is that's bothering you?
Father...
You're my father, my mother,
and my ancestor.
The rest is nothing for me
like the Gobi desert.
I'm a Mongol. I'll die fighting on
a horse like a real Mongol.
Nothing can change my love
and loyalty for you.
What is it, Alişar Bey?
You look surprised.
There's nothing to be surprised about.
We called you and you came.
Now we'll talk nicely.
Oh, nope. Dündar Bey looks like
he saw a monster.
May it be blessed.
You caused a lot of trouble.
Now, tell us what you want!
In our Tent, we want those
who are after a bloody war.
Give us my uncle Dündar and Bahadır.
And don't be involved in
our Tent's internal affairs.
If you want them,
you must get through me.
About your internal affairs...
Don't you know that all the Tents
in these lands are connected to me?
We're connected to our traditiıons
, not you, Alişar Bey.
We've come to these lands for holy war,
not for brute force.
You're talking about traditions.
But you don't know that...
... a Tent is connected to a Bey and a
Bey is connected to a Banner Lord, Gündüz.
Salurs, Dodurgas, AlkaEvlis
also live in these lands.
They don't cause trouble.
Why is it you who always causes trouble?
Remember this. This provision of yours
will be the rope that hangs you.
Are you threatening me?
Who do you think you are?
Pull yourselves together!
Alps!
Hear my words, Alişar.
Beys are not happy with you being
involved in Kayı's young men...
... assigning Beys, and trying to remove
a Bey from the throne with a bloody war.
They are scared as
to when it will be their turn.
Since the Turks are
so anxious and displeased...
... then as the Bey of these lands...
... I'll assign a Bey from the Çavdars!
Alişar Bey...
These lands are our sword-given rights.
What does it mean to make
a Mongol the land's Bey?
These lands belong to Geyhatu!
He takes the seal from
whoever he wants to.
And gives the throne
to whoever he wants to.
Do you think the Beys
in these lands will obey these orders?
This is the border, Alişar Bey!
Do you recognize?
It's not like the place you've come from.
Which of the Oghuz Tents will obey them?
They either bow
or get their heads cut off.
I said everything necessary.
You'll tell these to Geyhatu
when he personally stands in front of you.
You're trusting Geyhatu to protect you.
We're trusting Allah.
Come on, then.
Do everything you can.
Let's go!
By Allah! Let's go!
You found that dog's nest
since you came alone, Çetin.
We did thankfully, my Bey. Göktuğ is
with Balgay. He's waiting for us.
- Praise be! My lion!
- Thank you, my Bey!
But Balgay is crafty. He might realize
Göktuğ is working with us.
We shouldn't let a jackal strangle
our lion. Let's get going. Let's go!
It's too late. Geyhatu
will decide Kayı's fate.
It will be a little bloody. You'll
eventually get your throne, Dündar Bey.
You're right, Alişar Bey.
You're right.
- I'm worried about Melik.
- Alişar Bey...
... they either didn't fall into
the trap...
... or Melik, that master
hunter of yours, was hunted.
What if they made him talk like Zorba?
He knows a lot about our alliance.
Then I'll show them my wrath!
We're going into the woods!
We'll trace Melik!
Alps! Come on. Go this way.
My Bey! Someone is coming!
Keep your eyes open. Don't forget
what'll happen if they find us.
Let's go.
What's the situation, Göktuğ?
Balgay destroyed a unit of Geyhatu.
He's preparing to gather other units
that'll fight against him.
Geyhatu is preparing to kill Balgay
when he comes to Söğüt.
My Bey! Exactly as you wanted!
It's time to let dogs fight
each other, brothers.
Listen to me carefully.
The unit coming with Geyhatu
is very crowded.
It'll take your loyal commanders
days to come.
When Geyhatu comes,
I'll throw Kayıs at him first.
Kayıs are strong. While Geyhatu is busy
with causing Osman's extinction...
... my commanders will be here.
Then we'll start moving.
What about Osman?
You can't fight if you feel
the enemy on your back.
When Osman comes...
Ambush!
Balgay!
I didn't come here to take your life.
Listen to me carefully.
Won't you kill someone who betrayed you?
I want such a mighty commander
like you to have my back.
Yesterdays are over. Let's look ahead now.
Our enemies are the same.
That's why I'm here.
Geyhatu!
What do you want from me, Osman?
If we can agree, you'll give me
Alişar and I'll give you Geyhatu.
Our secret will remain hidden.
Lower your weapons.
Will we fight Geyhatu with
my handful of Nökers?
Remember. I also have a handful of Alps.
Geyhatu is coming here with an army.
How will we destroy a mighty
rock with a handful of sand?
If we become one, Geyhatu will be
the one who is scared.
Melik! You failed.
If I ever catch you...
Oh, Melik!
Alişar Bey! You can't catch Melik.
- Who sent you?
- Balgay did, Dündar Bey.
My Bey. Look.
During Batur Bey's funeral at the Tent,
we went after Osman.
Do you remember Balgay's man
who told us where Osman was?
Balgay found Osman.
He is on Kurt hill.
He called you.
Sencer! Keep your mouth shut.
We have tricks within tricks.
Gündüz couldn't have done this.
This is Osman's job, Alişar Bey!
Look! He tied him to a tree ;
so animals eat him!
How could Osman have done this?
Didn't commander Böke take him to Konya?
There's no one who can do this
other than Osman!
They'd be late to Söğüt if
they fought with Gündüz.
But they got there in time.
Alişar Bey!
I told you to take Osman's life there!
Can't you work out that .
Böke can't deal with Osman?
Dündar Bey!
I lost countless soldiers in this case!
What are you calling me out for?
Don't you remember everything
I've done for you?
I do, Alişar Bey.
I do.
But if Osman is back, I can't imagine
how much blood will be spilt.
You should remember that.
We can't beat Geyhatu's army. But that
doesn't mean we can't kill him.
- How?
- As Genghis Khan said...
If Turks begin to fight, they'll
trap Satan in hell.
- You trust yourself too much.
- I do if you're with me.
Besides, we won't be alone.
Kayıs and all the other
oppressed Tents will be with us.
But Alişar...
There are no issues if our
enemies are the same.
Alişar's poor life doesn't
mean anything to me.
I don't care about Geyhatu or
the wrecked Seljuk throne he's sitting on.
I want liberty in my Tent!
Then we'll go our separate ways.
Geyhatu sent a message
to Alişar with his commander.
We captured it this morning.
He ordered him to kill all the Kayıs and
hang you in the middle of Söğüt.
Many traitors' blood was spilt in Söğüt.
We'll see who hangs who when he
comes to Söğüt.
We're not alone. My commanders and Nökers
are on their way here to end Geyhatu.
They're coming. But don't assume
I forgot about Genghis Khan's laws.
We'll talk about it when the time comes.
First, we'll get you Geyhatu's throne.
And my Tent will get its liberty.
Then you'll get what you want.
How could I not see this until now?
- Are you sure about this, Sencer?
- I am, my Bey.
I still remember how he said,
"Balgay sent me."
Then Alişar Bey is lying to us.
You look bothered. What is it, father?
It's Alişar, son.
I think Alişar Bey has a plan for me.
Do you think he's trying to make a Kayı's
Bey because of his hatred towards Osman?
Politics, father. Why does it matter
when everyone wins?
These storms will stop once you
become a Bey.
They will. But keep your eyes open.
You're his right hand.
I'll hear about every step he takes.
Don't worry, father.
Commander Böke!
Take the horse inside! Go!
- Go.
- Commander Böke!
What happened? Are you okay?
Balgay attacked!
He took Osman.
I hardly escaped.
Both of them are condemned
to stay together to stay alive.
Either Geyhatu will kill all the Kayıs,
or you'll be quick and get your Tent back!
There's no other way!
I know where Balgay and Osman are.
I found out about Osman's nest.
I followed them.
We can wipe them with a sudden ambush!
Tell me, Commander Böke.
Tell me!
Bamsı Bey, what's our situation?
Are the covers at the entrance ready?
They're ready, Gündüz Bey.
The covers are ready.
the quivers are full of arrows.
Swords are sharp.
Even our breaths are ready!
Bless you!
This time our fight is with our own blood.
I know both of you had good times
with my uncle Dündar.
What do your hearts say about this fight?
We went and return such
battlefields as men, thank Allah.
Dündar was with us in some of them.
But our friendship will continue...
... as long as we're on the same path.
For this reason...
... if someone leaves this path...
... it's our duty to hit them
like a ton of bricks.
Remember this.
That's what our hearts say.
- Thank you.
- Our goal...
... is to bring prosperity to Kayı,
Gündüz Bey.
We want nothing more than Allah's sake,
our Tent's peace...
... and our hearts' happiness.
Our blood will boil if it's about
our Tent's future, my Gündüz.
Thank you, Abdurrahman Gazi.
Praise be! Then...
... I'll make your blood boil even more
with a message.
What is it, son? What message is it?
I received a blessed message.
Guys...
We're invited to a wedding.
- What wedding?
- I hope nothing is wrong.
One of Sheikh Edebali's Dervishes came.
Bala Hatun and our Osman Bey will marry.
They're expecting you to come too,
he said.
- How wonderful!
- What are you saying?
What are you saying, my Gündüz?
What are you saying?
- Wonderful! Abdurrahman Gazi!
- How wonderful, Bamsı brother!
My dark-eyes Osman!
My valiant with the looks of an eagle!
My Osman will form his own tent!
Will create his own house!
Just when he was putting his
life out for his Tent...
... he'll bring new lives to Kayı.
New lives!
- May Allah protect him!
- Amen.
May Allah make our Osman live
a long, fortunate life!
How nice of a valiant he become!
Thank Allah.
May Allah give him
dutiful children like himself!
- Allah willing!
- Allah willing, Abdurrahman Gazi!
Come on. It's time to prepare.
Bamsı Bey.
Take the best precautions possible.
Abdurrahman Gazi. Take Alps
to take their positions.
We'll go to the wedding secretly.
No one will know.
Okay, Gündüz Bey.
How wonderful! Let me take a look at you!
It looks wonderful on you.
Praise be my girl.
My beautiful daughter.
I wish my mother Ulduz was with me.
I wish she saw my happiness, Selcan Hatun.
My beautiful daughter.
My Osman is an orphan just like you.
I wish his sons saw this day.
But thankfully I'm here
to see this moment.
Your elders have rights in this moment.
I need to say what they
must have said to you. Come with me.
It's easy to create a home, my daughter.
It's hard to keep it standing.
The wife's troubles are different,
the husband's troubles are different.
The real craft is
to understand those troubles...
... and be a companion to your husband.
If you see a strong household,
know that there is a strong wife in there.
The husband comes after the wife
inside the house.
The female creates the house,
the husband makes it famous.
Protect your home, my beautiful daughter.
Look after your home and your man.
May my almighty Allah bless you
with beautiful children.
And long lives for you
to look after those children.
Don't be upset! You became a friend to
me and a companion for my Osman.
I'm your mother from now on.
Thankfully, Selcan mother.
I'm still too young. Be my guide so you
can correct me when I'm wrong.
Show the path to me when I'm mistaken.
Hopefully.
Bala! There can be no brides
without hennas, my daughter! Let's go.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim
(in the name of God, the merciful and compassionate.)
How wonderful!
Commander Böke!
Tell me.
I deceived Alişar.
He' and Dündar Bey will fall into the
trap of Osman Bey.
Really?
It's not that easy.
Why?
Alişar will gather all of his soldiers.
Like a pitched battle? Huh?
Even worse.
We can't cope with them if Balgay's
soldiers don't catch.
Don't worry about these, Commander Böke.
Osman Bey must've known something.
Go to the palace now. They shouldn'
t get suspicious.
Osman bey got you, Alişar.
"I bear witness that there is no deity but Allah...
and I bear witness that Muhammad is
the messenger of Allah" -Shahada.
Bala Hatun, daughter of Sheikh Edebalı...
do you accept to marry
Osman, son of Ertuğrul Ghazi...
in exchange for him giving 200 dram golden...
as a bride price?
- I do.
- Do you accept?
Osman, son of Ertuğrul Ghazi...
do you accept to marry Bala Hatun....
who is the daughter of Sheikh Edebalı?
I do.
- Do you accept?
- I do.
You as witnesses...
Abdurrahman Ghazi, Zülfikar Dervish...
do you act as a witnesses?
- I do.
Then I solemnize your marriage...
in the presence of witnesses here.
May Allah bless your marriage.
- Amin.
Mashaallah, my valiant.
To Allah...
to our Prophet, Mohammad...
may
peace be upon him.
- Amin.
- My Allah, bless this marriage.
Give them respect for each other and...
perseverance for their marriage.
- Amin.
Don't give them hate and dissension.
Amin.
- May Allah bless us.
- Amin.
May Allah make your house...
full of knowledge and wisdom.
- Amin.
I know and believe that...
your marriage isn't just an agreement.
It's a pearl of holy wisdom.
May Allah make you and your descendants...
soldiers for Allah's way.
- Amin.
" Exalted is your Lord, the Lord of
might, above what they describe...
...and peace upon the messengers...
...And praise to Allah, Lord of the
worlds. Al Fatihah. " Surah As- Saffat.
Erlik Khan, make Cenghiz Khan's
soul our leader.
Let our swords
speak, let the death shut up.
It's complicated.
Everything became so complicated.
May Allah grant us to
ride out the storm...
and get rid of the burdens, Inshaallah.
Inshaallah, Aygül.
Inshaallah.
Burçin...
What will you wish when
we ride out the storm?
- What do you want to happen?
- What should I?
I want our old order.
No.
I think you think of something else.
You have other wishes.
Your hearts wants someone.
I think you know.
But, pull yourself together.
What are you talking about, mother?
Burçin.
What does your heart want?
You think of Bahadır brother...
No.
Good.
It shouldn't happen.
Look.
You think he is like a mountain but...
mountains are heavy.
Why don't you ever speak of good things?
You always think bad.
Don't you see how much my
Bahadır brother has changed?
Do you see, Aygül?
Don't be sure.
Those eyes have seen much, you know.
A person's nature doesn't change.
Ever.
Bahadır isn't reliable.
You'll wait.
You'll see.
Okay, mother.
You've said enough.
Burçin.
Listen to your heart.
My mother is angry with my brother.
She always thinks of old things.
That's why she's angry.
I trust Bahadır brother.
May Allah grant you the best.
My Bala.
My beginning.
My end. My yesterday, my tomorrow.
My dream, my reality.
And my only wish.
Welcome to my life and heart.
Osman.
I never gave up.
I never gave up on my love.
Your name became my prayer.
My heart was so full of that prayer.
Thank Allah that we came to these days.
From now on, I wish to
close and open my eyes with you.
I wish our Allah treat us with His mercy.
I wish he makes us grow together
and raise.
Believe me, my Bala.
Believe me.
Allah will grant us...
girls and boys who will run in our tent
and maintain our lineage.
Believe it as I do.
Believe it as I believe it.
Our destiny will be good.
Our tent will be good.
Our souls will always be in these lands.
But first we'll kill people...
who are trying to harm our tent.
We'll kill people who want to kill us.
Your way is my way, Osman.
I'll follow you wherever you go.
If you give me duty, I'll deal with it.
- Don't hesitate about me.
- Why should I, my Bala?
You're my reason to praise.
I take my power from my Allah...
and then you.
May Allah grant me to bring Alişar
down a peg...
and kill him...
and then...
make me come back to you.
- Inshaallah.
Inshaallah.
Bala.
Take care of yourself.
Wait for me, Hatun.
I'll wait for you my whole life, Bey.
May Allah help you on your way.
Come and back fast.
Inshaallah.
My Bey...
Take this.
This is Batur brother's dagger.
This dagger
is entrusted to you like my revenge.
I know that everything I've
entrusted to you is safe.
You talk as if you haven't put
off your hijab.
I don't hold a grudge against Gündüz Ağa
and Bamsı Bey.
My problem is with Osman.
There's blood between us.
I can't keep calm even if I drink
Osman's blood.
I wish...
that you'll shed that murderer's
blood with my brother's dagger.
You wish and...
I can fill this pool with not
only Osman's blood...
but also everyone's blood if they're
after Osman.
Then go and come
back with glory.
May your sword be sharp.
Let everyone see who's
controlling this land.
We went through hoops together.
We shared happiness.
You've always prayed for us.
Now...
always pray for us, my Sheikh.
We...
walk the same way with the same goal.
Our prayers and support will
always be with you, son.
My precious ones.
They're entrusted to Allah and then you.
Inshaallah, I'll come back
from this war and...
take my entrustments from you.
We've entrusted our lives to each other.
We'll protect them.
Don't worry, Osman Bey.
Thanks.
May my Allah support you, who's
going to the war for freedom...
with his invisible army.
Go and come back with prosperity.
Thank you, my Sheikh.
Everyone here...
witness that...
not even a single one of us is after...
his own desires.
Our goal...
is to bring these lands justice and peace.
Now...
give me your blessings.
- We do.
- Give me your blessings.
We do.
Come on!
Infidels that stand against us!
They will find Hamza's courage...
Yasin's guts, Ammar's tenacity here.
I swear that our aim is independence...
our armor is shahada!
Justice forever!
Independence forever!
Allah is the greatest!
Ey, son.
Remember, our path is for ever.
Our aim is to conquer hearts.
Our case is to be vassal (of Allah)
Ey, son.
Be the justice in the shadow of crescent.
Destroy the cruels.
Help the oppressed.
Dominate the wars and be veteran,
be the state!
Ey son.
Be Bey to your community.
Be the conqueror for oppressed ones.
Be cruel to the cruels.
Be the peace.
Be the state of the states!
Please contact turkision@gmail.com
for any inquiries